{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Automatic Blind \u0026 Drape Installers","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40468/":{"taskOID":40468,"originalTaskOID":40468,"setID":756,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":1084,"questionDisplayText":"Rooms in Need of Blinds/Shades","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"In which rooms would you like to install blinds or shades? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":1003,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Bedroom","answerDisplayText":"Bedroom","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3412,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Kitchen","answerDisplayText":"Kitchen","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3628,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Living room","answerDisplayText":"Living room","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2380,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Family room","answerDisplayText":"Family room","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1926,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Dining room","answerDisplayText":"Dining room","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":983,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Bathroom","answerDisplayText":"Bathroom","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3052,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Home office","answerDisplayText":"Home office","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":1086,"questionDisplayText":"Window mount type","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of mount will these windows be?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":3224,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Inside","answerDisplayText":"Inside","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4488,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Outside","answerDisplayText":"Outside","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":1084,"questionDisplayText":"Rooms in Need of Blinds/Shades","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"In which rooms would you like to install blinds or shades? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":1003,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Bedroom","answerDisplayText":"Bedroom","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3412,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Kitchen","answerDisplayText":"Kitchen","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3628,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Living room","answerDisplayText":"Living room","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2380,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Family room","answerDisplayText":"Family room","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1926,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Dining room","answerDisplayText":"Dining room","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":983,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Bathroom","answerDisplayText":"Bathroom","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3052,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Home office","answerDisplayText":"Home office","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":1003,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Bedroom","answerDisplayText":"Bedroom","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3412,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Kitchen","answerDisplayText":"Kitchen","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3628,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Living room","answerDisplayText":"Living room","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2380,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Family room","answerDisplayText":"Family room","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1926,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Dining room","answerDisplayText":"Dining room","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":983,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Bathroom","answerDisplayText":"Bathroom","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3052,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Home office","answerDisplayText":"Home office","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":1086,"questionDisplayText":"Window mount type","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of mount will these windows be?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":3224,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Inside","answerDisplayText":"Inside","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4488,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Outside","answerDisplayText":"Outside","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":3224,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Inside","answerDisplayText":"Inside","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4488,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Outside","answerDisplayText":"Outside","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"__cache./api/resource/task/40468/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40468,"taskName":"Electronic Drape, Shade or Blind Opener - Install","taskDescription":"Install Automatic Drape, Shade or Blind Opener","xmTaskDescriptor":"Automatic Blind \u0026 Drape Installers","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":275,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Electric Motorized Blinds Drape vertical","textMessagingName":"Inst Elec Window","rolloverLongDesc":"Devices can be controlled by timers, button, remote control or computers.","rolloverShortDesc":"Includes replacing an existing device.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Install Automatic Drape, Shade or Blind Opener.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Automatic Blind \u0026 Drape Installation \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Electric Blinds \u0026 Drapes","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":24,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":5,"bridgeTaskOid":39794,"bridgeTaskText":"Note: If your repair is not very complex or you have a variety of small projects, you might consider ","bridgeTaskLinkText":"requesting a Handyman.","bridgeTaskLinkId":1437,"bridgeTaskActive":"Y","xmName":"Electronic Drapes, Shades or Blinds Install","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Electronic Drape, Shade or Blind Opener - Install","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Electronic Drapes or Shade Project","urlName":"Electronic-Drape-Shade-or-Blind-Opener-Install","taskConsiderationId":2,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Automatic Blind \u0026 Drape Installers - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | HomeAdvisor Costs \u0026 Reviews","searchKeywords":"Electric,Motorized,Blinds,Drape,vertical,drapes,draperies,custom,Opener,Shade,Electronic,Window,electrician","emcCategoryOid":-12079,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":756,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}